<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Team Unicorn]]></title>
  <link href="http://rgsoc.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://rgsoc.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2013-07-23T17:15:37+02:00</updated>
  <id>http://rgsoc.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[More active]]></title>
    <link href="http://rgsoc.github.io/blog/2013/07/23/more-active/"/>
    <updated>2013-07-23T15:10:00+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://rgsoc.github.io/blog/2013/07/23/more-active</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Today we were planning on how to actually make our blog Team Unicorn more active, how to structure the posts and push our new layout (thanks to Hester!). On Friday Victoria will finally learn how to post on the blog!</p>

<p>We also had our first planning about Spree project (yay!) It will be very changelling but a lot of fun!!
Soon we will make our baby steps into the project :)</p>

<p>More news coming soon, stay tuned!
Hester &amp; Victoria</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update!]]></title>
    <link href="http://rgsoc.github.io/blog/2013/07/23/update/"/>
    <updated>2013-07-23T15:05:00+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://rgsoc.github.io/blog/2013/07/23/update</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>It had been a long time since our last post, but summer holidays and a lot of work was in the middle… Let’s start from the beginning, shall we?</p>

<p>Hester and I had been pretty busy, still dealing with Zombies, we enrolled at Code School and our goal is to pass all Ruby courses before that our brains are eaten by those zombies!
Our coach, Peter, was on holidays, so we were planning to work hard during his absence, but not always what you plan is what actually happens. I got a new job that keeps me busier than I expected and Hester was working hard and afterwards she left on holidays (very well deserved!)</p>

<p>In the meantime, we continue slowly but steady with our tutorials, I was reading books about Ruby on Rails and trying small exercises.
Our big day was when we went to the Ruby 101 course in Amsterdam, thanks to Amsterdam-rb. It was a very fun day where I finally met Hester in person and together with 5 other people we spent the whole day coding and learning new stuff.
This course helped us to put in order most of the knowledge that we had and also gave us a boost of motivation to continue.</p>

<p>Next big milestone was Monday 22nd when everyone is back to work and we had our interview with Spree project!</p>

<p>Victoria and Hester</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2 days in 1]]></title>
    <link href="http://rgsoc.github.io/blog/2013/07/04/two-days-in-one/"/>
    <updated>2013-07-04T09:41:00+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://rgsoc.github.io/blog/2013/07/04/two-days-in-one</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>We didn&rsquo;t post during the last 2 days so here you have our reason and also what we had been doing&hellip;</p>

<p>On Tuesday, Victoria went to The Hague with Floor Drees to see where the Rails Girls The Hague will take place. It is a great place! and the event will rock in September!
Hester was working hard to have spare time on Wednesday to continue coding.</p>

<p>On Wednesday, we continued coding (from 10am to 5pm), subscribed to Code School to do all courses. Yes, we love those zombies after all! What we learn is that Ruby on Rails can be very funny if you have the chance to code with a friend and that time flies when you do it!</p>

<p>Today more coding and more lessons will come, what will we learn? Still a mystery&hellip; stay tuned!</p>

<p>Oh! also Rails Girls Groningen and Rails Girls Eindhoven events are on the table for the next months! :)</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[first test!]]></title>
    <link href="http://rgsoc.github.io/blog/2013/07/03/first-test/"/>
    <updated>2013-07-03T16:52:00+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://rgsoc.github.io/blog/2013/07/03/first-test</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hello!</p>

<p>Second day of coding today, it&rsquo;s getting a bit harder&hellip; We finished the rails for zombies tutorial and started on the rails for zombies 2.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[First day of Rails Girls Summer of Code.]]></title>
    <link href="http://rgsoc.github.io/blog/2013/07/01/first-day-of-rails-girls-summer-of-code/"/>
    <updated>2013-07-01T21:14:00+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://rgsoc.github.io/blog/2013/07/01/first-day-of-rails-girls-summer-of-code</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Still with a low level of coffee in our systems, we started our Google hangout at 11:30am. At the beginning we didn’t know where to start or what to do, so we started with the Code School tutorial, Rails for Zombies. It was a lot of fun and learning!</p>

<p>We also took the picture for the newsletter of Rails Girls Summer of Code, and we aren’t sure yet what was more difficult if the coding or take a picture that we both like!</p>

<p>Our first day was a lot of fun, sharing, coding and a perfect start for the rest of the summer.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
